Guide to the Danbury, Town of Records 1892-1969 DRG 1 DRG.1
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series VI: Selectmen, Board of 1914-1960/DG179 & DG 209, 26930
  - Selectmen Records, 1920-1955, 26931
    - Gasoline Stations, Used Car & Repairer's Notices & Junk Yards, Blueprint: Sun Oil Company, (Edward J. Henry), August 23, 1946; 27058 (Folder OS Folder 1.1, Item 6)
    - Gasoline Station Application, Map: Map of property to be conveyed to Herbert W. Barlow by West Terrace Realty Co., Lake Avenue Extension. June 23, 1953; 27056 (Folder OS Folder 1.1, Item 7)
    - Gasoline Station Application, Blueprint: The Texaco Company, Lake Avenue Ext. & Old Lake Avenue, undated; 27055 (Folder OS Folder 1.1, Item 8)
    - Gasoline Station Application, Blueprints (5): The Texaco Company, Type "EM" Service Station, 1947-1949; 27054 (Folder OS Folder 1.1, Item 9)
    - Gasoline Station Application, Herbert W. Barlow, 1953; 27057 (Box 15, Folder 124-125)
    - Gas Stations & Used Car Lots Misc., 1931-1946; 27053 (Box 15, Folder 126-128)
    - GE-GR Misc., 1921-1948; 27052 (Box 15, Folder 129-131)
    - Grimes, Walter, 1937; 27051 (Box 15, Folder 132)
    - GU Misc., 1931-1959; 27050 (Box 15, Folder 133)
    - HA Misc., 1931-1957; 27049 (Box 15, Folder 134-136)
    - HE Misc., 1931-1954; 27048 (Box 15, Folder 137)
    - HO Misc., 1932-1959; 27047 (Box 15, Folder 138)
    - HU-HY Misc., 1931-1941; 27046 (Box 15, Folder 139)
    - Information Requests, 1951-1960; 27045 (Box 15, Folder 140)
    - I-J Misc., 1929-1945; 27044 (Box 15, Folder 141)
    - KA-KE Misc., 1930-1956; 27043 (Box 15, Folder 142)
    - KI-KZ Misc., 1935-1947; 27042 (Box 15, Folder 143)
    - L-LI Misc., 1931-1952; 27041 (Box 15, Folder 144)
    - LI-LZ Misc., 1931-1954; 27040 (Box 15, Folder 145-146)
    - MA Misc., 1931-1959; 27039 (Box 15, Folder 147)
    - Mc Misc., 1931-1949; 27038 (Box 15, Folder 148)
    - ME-MI Misc., 1930-1957; 27037 (Box 15, Folder 149-150)
    - MO-MU Misc., 1925-1949; 27036 (Box 15, Folder 151-152)
    - NA-NI Misc., 1928-1958; 27035 (Box 15, Folder 153-155)
    - New Industries Applicants, 1941-1947; 27034 (Box 15, Folder 156)
    - NO-NZ Misc., 1931-1946; 27033 (Box 15, Folder 157)
    - O Misc., 1931-1959; 27032 (Box 15, Folder 158)
    - Old Age Tax Assessment, 1944-1960; 27031 (Box 15, Folder 159-161)
    - Office of Defense Transportation & Emergency Management, 1943-1945; 27030 (Box 15, Folder 162)
    - PA-PI Misc., 1918-1953; 27029 (Box 15, Folder 163)
    - Park Avenue School, 1950-1955; 27028 (Box 15, Folder 164)
    - Permits - Opening of Roads, 1931-1939; 27027 (Box 15, Folder 165-166)
    - Permits - Opening of Roads, 1940-1943; 27026 (Box 15, Folder 167)
    - Permits - Opening of Roads, 1944-1947; 27025 (Box 15, Folder 168)
    - Permits - Opening of Roads, 1948-1951; 27024 (Box 15, Folder 169-171)
    - Permits - Opening of Roads, 1952-1953; 27023 (Box 15, Folder 172)
    - Permits - Opening of Roads, 1954-1955; 27022 (Box 15, Folder 173-174)
    - Permits - Opening of Roads, 1956-1957; 27021 (Box 15, Folder 175-176)
    - Permits - Opening of Roads, 1958-1959; 27020 (Box 15, Folder 177-178)
    - PL-PZ Misc., 1931-1945; 27019 (Box 16, Folder 179)
    - Prices (as of March 1st 1942), 27018 (Box 16, Folder 180)
    - Q Misc., 1914-1922; 27017 (Box 16, Folder 181)
    - R-RI Misc., 1925-1957; 27016 (Box 16, Folder 182-184)
    - Rationing Board, 1942-1943; 27015 (Box 16, Folder 185)
    - Relief Cases Approved by Selectman, 1931-1932; 27014 (Folder OS Folder 1.1, Item *)
    - Rental Dwellings, Registration of & Rent Control Data, Red Cross, "Returned Veterans" & War Memorial, 1945-1952; 27013 (Box 16, Folder 186)
    - RO-RZ Misc., 1931-1958; 27012 (Box 16, Folder 187)
    - SA-SC Misc., 1935-1957; 27011 (Box 16, Folder 188)
    - SE Misc., 1931-1949; 27010 (Box 16, Folder 189-190)
    - SH-SN Misc., 1930-1945; 27009 (Box 16, Folder 191)
    - Social Security, 1951-1952; 27008 (Box 16, Folder 192)
    - South Street & Morris Street Schools, 1936-1957; 27007 (Box 16, Folder 193)
    - ST-SZ Misc., 1930-1960; 27006 (Box 16, Folder 194-196)
    - Standard Oil Company, 1931-1940; 27005 (Box 16, Folder 197)
    - State of Connecticut, Commodities, 1934-1940; 27004 (Box 16, Folder 198)
    - State of Connecticut, Development Commission, 1947; 27003 (Box 16, Folder 198a)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, 1929-1930; 27002 (Box 16, Folder 199)
    - Blueprint: Danbury/Newtown Road, November 30, 1930; 27001 (Folder OS Folder 1.1)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, 1931; 27000 (Box 16, Folder 200)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, 1932; 26999 (Box 16, Folder 201-202)
    - Blueprint: Brewster Road, July 20, 1932; 26998 (Folder OS Folder 1.1)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, 1934-1935; 26997 (Box 16, Folder 203-204)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, 1935-1937; 26996 (Box 16, Folder 205)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, 1938-1939; 26995 (Box 16, Folder 206)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, 1940; 26994 (Box 16, Folder 207)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, WPA Project #3644, 1941; 26993 (Box 16, Folder 208-209)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, 1941; 26992 (Box 16, Folder 210-213)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, 1942; 26991 (Box 16, Folder 214-215)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, 1943; 26990 (Box 16, Folder 216-218)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, 1944; 26989 (Box 16, Folder 219-220)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, 1945; 26988 (Box 16, Folder 221-223)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, 1946; 26987 (Box 16, Folder 224-228)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, 1947; 26986 (Box 16, Folder 229-231)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, 1948; 26985 (Box 16, Folder 232-234)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, Map of City of Danbury, undated; 26984 (Folder OS Folder 1.1, Item 10)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, 1949; 26983 (Box 16, Folder 235-236)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, Maps: Danbury-Newtown Road, 1931; 26982 (Folder OS Folder 1.1, Item 11)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, Map: Brewster Road in Danbury, 1931; 26981 (Folder OS Folder 1.1, Item 12)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, 1950; 26980 (Box 17, Folder 237-238)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, 1951; 26979 (Box 17, Folder 239-244)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, 1952; 26978 (Box 17, Folder 245-247)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, 1953; 26977 (Box 17, Folder 248-250)
    - State of Connecticut, Highway Department, 1954; 26976 (Box 17, Folder 251-253)
    - State of Connecticut, Labor Department, 1944-1957; 26975 (Box 17, Folder 254)
    - State of Connecticut, State Park & Forest Commission, 1931-1956; 26974 (Box 17, Folder 255)
    - State of Connecticut, State Park & Forest Commission, Map: Kellogg Property, Wooster Heights, undated; 26973 (Folder OS Folder 5.1, Item 1)
    - State of Connecticut, State Police & DMV, & Traffic Commission, 1931-1949; 26972 (Box 17, Folder 256-258)
    - State of Connecticut, Public Welfare, 1923-1934; 26971 (Box 17, Folder 259-260)
    - State of Connecticut, Public Welfare, 1935-1939; 26970 (Box 17, Folder 261)
    - State of Connecticut, Public Welfare, 1940-1948; 26969 (Box 17, Folder 262-264)
    - State of Connecticut, Public Welfare, 1949-1951; 26968 (Box 17, Folder 265-267)
    - State of Connecticut, Public Welfare, 1952-1953; 26967 (Box 17, Folder 268-270)
    - State of Connecticut, Tax Commissioner, 1913-1923; 26966 (Box 17, Folder 271-273)
    - State of Connecticut, Tax Commissioner, 1924-1930; 26965 (Box 17, Folder 274-276)
    - State of Connecticut, Tax Commissioner, 1931-1934; 26964 (Box 17, Folder 277-279)
    - State of Connecticut, Tax Commissioner, 1935-1937; 26963 (Box 17, Folder 280)
    - State of Connecticut, Tax Commissioner, 1938-1941; 26962 (Box 17, Folder 281)
    - State of Connecticut, Tax Commissioner, 1942-1944; 26961 (Box 17, Folder 282-283)
    - State of Connecticut, Tax Commissioner, 1945-1949; 26960 (Box 17, Folder 284-285)
    - State of Connecticut, Tax Commissioner, 1951-1956; 26959 (Box 17, Folder 286)
    - State and Town Department of Health, 1931-1949; 26958 (Box 17, Folder 287-290)
    - Surplus Commodities, 1946-1947; 26957 (Box 17, Folder 291)
    - TA-TZ Misc., 1929-1952; 26956 (Box 17, Folder 292-295)
    - Tax Collector's Office, 1918-1959; 26955 (Box 18, Folder 296)
    - Tax Collector's Office, 1947-1948; 26954 (Box 18, Folder 297-298)
    - Tax Collector's Office, 1945-1946; 26953 (Box 18, Folder 299-300)
    - Tax Collector's Office, 1942-1944; 26952 (Box 18, Folder 301-302)
    - Tax Collector's Office, 1940-1941; 26951 (Box 18, Folder 303)
    - Tax Collector's Office, 1935-1938; 26950 (Box 18, Folder 304)
    - To Whom It May Concern & Recommendations, Form Letters, 1939-1957; 26949 (Box 18, Folder 305-307)
    - The Travelers, 1933-1951; 26948 (Box 18, Folder 308)
    - Tree Warden (Benjamin A. Mancuso & Harry Morris), 1933-1949; 26947 (Box 18, Folder 309-311)
    - Tree Work--The Albert W. Meserve Company, 1944-1948; 26946 (Box 18, Folder 312)
    - U Misc., 1913-1948; 26945 (Box 18, Folder 313)
    - V Misc., 1921-1948; 26944 (Box 18, Folder 314)
    - Veterans Home & Hospital Commission, 1952-1954; 26943 (Box 19, Folder 315-316)
    - Veterans Home & Hospital Commission, 1948-1951; 26942 (Box 19, Folder 317-318)
    - Veterans Home & Hospital Commission, 1943-1947; 26941 (Box 19, Folder 319-320)
    - Veterans Home & Hospital Commission, 1940-1942; 26940 (Box 19, Folder 321)
    - Veterans Home & Hospital Commission, 1936-1939; 26939 (Box 19, Folder 322)
    - Veterans Home & Hospital Commission, 1914-1935; 26938 (Box 19, Folder 323)
    - WA-WE Misc., 1915-1944; 26937 (Box 19, Folder 324-326)
    - WH-WY Misc., 1914-1950; 26936 (Box 19, Folder 327-329)
    - Works Progress Administration, 1936-1938; 26935 (Box 19, Folder 330)
    - W.P.A. and P.W.A. (Federal) Airport, 1931-1942; 26934 (Box 19, Folder 331)
    - Y Miscellaneous, 1916-1944; 26933 (Box 19, Folder 332)
    - Zoning Board, 1938-1944; 26932 (Box 19, Folder 333)
- Series VII: Justice Docket (Aaron Bates), 49835
  - Justice Docket, 1893-1897; 26216 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Aaron T. Bates, Justice of the Peace.
  - Justice Docket, 1897-1900, 1903-1907; 26215 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Civil Cases, 1900-1917, 26214 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Justice Docket, 1911; 26213 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Aaron T. Bates, Justice of the Peace. 3 cases recorded.